There is a reason they woke up.
Passengers is a drama, romance, science fiction film directed by Morten Tyldum.
A spacecraft traveling to a distant colony planet and transporting
thousands of people has a malfunction in its sleep chambers.
As a result, two passengers are awakened 90 years early.
Aurora Lane, played by Jennifer Lawrence.
Jim Preston, played by Chris Pratt.
Arthur, played by Michael Sheen.
Gus Mancuso, played by Laurence Fishburne.
Captain Norris, played by Andy Garcia.
Executive Officer, played by Vince Foster.
Passengers is a 2016 American science fiction romance film directed by Morten Tyldum,
written by Jon Spaihts and starring Jennifer Lawrence and Chris Pratt.
The supporting cast includes Michael Sheen, Laurence Fishburne, and Andy Garcia.
The film follows two passengers on an interstellar spacecraft carrying thousands of people to a colony
120-years-traveling-distance from Earth, when the two are awakened 90 years early from their suspended hibernation.
The script was written by Spaihts in 2007, but languished in development, with multiple actors attached
to it over the years until Sony Pictures Entertainment acquired the rights in late 2014.
Lawrence, Pratt and Tyldum joined the project shortly thereafter, and filming
took place from September 2015 to February 2016 in Atlanta.
Passengers premiered at the Regency Village Theater in Los Angeles on December 14, 2016, and was
released theatrically in the United States by Columbia Pictures on December 21.
The film received mixed reviews from critics, although the performances of
Lawrence and Pratt were praised, and grossed $303 million.
It was nominated for Best Original Score and Best
Production Design at the 89th Academy Awards.
The film explores themes of android, spacecraft, asteroid, isolation, shower.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and thought_provoking.